Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America records
1950-1970
1959-1969
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
3235
3235-001
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
2.83 cubic feet (4 boxes)
Correspondence, hearing transcripts and case files of a labor organization
Correspondence, hearing transcripts and case files. Files are of Jack Goldberger, general organizer for the Teamsters, based in San Francisco. Correspondence is with Teamster headquarters and locals, mainly in California and the Southwest.
Open to all users.
Donated by Jack Goldberger, 1/1/1980.
Hoffa, James R. (James Riddle), 1913-; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; California
- Interoffice Correspondence (Box-folder 1/1-9)
  - Teamsters, International Brotherhood, 1959-67
- Incoming Letters (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Brundage, Hackler, & Roseman. San Francisco, CA, 1962-64
- Hearing Transcripts (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Hearing Panel. Teamsters Joint Council 42. Jurisdictional Committee, 1966-67
- Subject Series
  - D.R.I.V.E., 1963-64 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute Between Local 208 and Local 196. Quikway Service. Los Angeles, CA, 1958-63 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - National Conference of Newspaper, Magazine Drivers and Handlers. Detroit, MI, 1965-66 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - National Pipeline Agreement, 1969 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Pacific Motor Trucking Company. Master File. Oakland, CA, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 2/3-4)
  - Santa Anita. Race Tracks. California, 1964-67 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Teamsters. Arline Division, 1963-67 (Box-folder 2/6-7)
  - Teamsters. Joint Council 7-38. (Construction), 1965 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - United Parcel Delivery Service Strike. November 17, 1958, 1958-70 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Local 9. San Francisco, CA, 1967-68 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Local 12., 1963-66 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Local 14. Las Vegas, NV, 1964-67 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Local 20. Toledo, OH, 1963 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Local 52., undated (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Local 70. Oakland, CA, 1961-69 (Box-folder 3/6-8)
  - Local 78. Alameda, Napa, and Solano Counties, 1966-69 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Local 83. Phoenix, AZ, 1959-69 (Box-folder 3/10-11)
  - Local 85. San Francisco, CA, 1951-68 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Local 88. Las Vegas, NV, 1966 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Local 94. Visalia, CA, 1965 (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Local 96. Castro Valley, CA, 1964 (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Local 102. Newark, NJ, 1961 (Box-folder 3/16)
  - Local 104, 1964-65 (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Local 107. Philadelphia, PA, undated (Box-folder 3/18)
  - Local 109. San Francisco, CA, 1961-65 (Box-folder 3/19)
  - Local 146. Colorado Springs, CO, 1962 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Local 148. Wenatchee, WA, 1965 (Box-folder 3/21)
  - Local 150. Sacramento, CA, 1962-69 (Box-folder 3/22)
  - Local 162, 1964 (Box-folder 3/23)
  - Local 174. Seattle, WA, 1960-65 (Box-folder 3/24)
  - Local 180., 1961-62 (Box-folder 3/25)
  - Local 186. Santa Barbara, CA, 1962 (Box-folder 3/26)
  - Local 197. Cleveland, OH, 1964 (Box-folder 3/27)
  - Local 203. Los Angeles, CA, 1964-65 (Box-folder 3/28)
  - Local 208. Los Angeles, CA, 1961-70 (Box-folder 3/29-32)
  - Local 209. Alameda, CA, 1961-70 (Box-folder 3/33)
  - Local 216. San Francisco, CA, 1961-69 (Box-folder 3/34)
  - Local 219. Denver, CO, 1964 (Box-folder 3/35)
  - Local 222. Salt Lake City, UT, 1966 (Box-folder 3/36)
  - Local 224. Los Angeles, CA, 1963-65 (Box-folder 3/37)
  - Local 238. Cedar Rapids, IA, 1964 (Box-folder 3/38)
  - Local 239. New York, NY, 1962 (Box-folder 3/39)
  - Local 241. San Francisco, CA, 1961-69 (Box-folder 3/40)
  - Local 256. San Francisco, CA, 1962-70 (Box-folder 3/41)
  - Local 265 San Francisco, CA, 1960-65 (Box-folder 3/42)
  - Local 268. Philadelphia, PA, 1966 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Local 278. San Francisco, CA, 1962-69 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Local 287. San Jose, CA, 1961-65 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Local 291. Oakland, CA, 1964 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Local 292. Deming, NM, 1961-63 (Box-folder 4/5-7)
  - Local 296. San Jose, CA, 1963-70 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Local 299. Detroit, MI, 1962-69 (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Local 306. Los Angeles, CA, 1962 (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Local 310. Tucson, AZ, 1962-64 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Local 315. Martinez, CA, 1962-68 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Local 334. Spokane, WA, 1962-65 (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Local 353. Seattle, WA, 1962 (Box-folder 4/14)
  - Local 372., 1967 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Local 381. Santa Maria, CA, 1962 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - Local 389., 1962-63 (Box-folder 4/17)
  - Local 390. Miami, FL, 1963 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Local 399., 1962 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Local 420. Los Angeles, 1962-65 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - Local 431. Fresno, CA, 1962 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Local 432. Oakland, CA, 1966 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Local 439. Stockton, CA, 1960-66 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - Local 440., undated (Box-folder 4/24)
  - Local 465. Seattle, WA, 1960 (Box-folder 4/25)
  - Local 467, 1962 (Box-folder 4/26)
  - Local 468. San Francisco, CA, 1961-67 (Box-folder 4/27)
  - Local 473., 1968 (Box-folder 4/28)
  - Local 490. Vallejo, CA, 1963 (Box-folder 4/29)
  - Local 495. Los Angeles, CA, 1961-65 (Box-folder 4/30)
  - Local 533. Reno, NV, 1962 (Box-folder 4/31)
  - Local 547., 1964 (Box-folder 4/32)
  - Local 576. San Jose, CA, 1950-60 (Box-folder 4/33)
  - Local 595., 1962-64 (Box-folder 4/34)
  - Local 598. Los Angeles, CA, 1964-66 (Box-folder 4/35)
  - Local 606. Los Angeles, CA, 1963-66 (Box-folder 4/36)
  - Local 618. St. Louis, MO, 1960 (Box-folder 4/37)
  - Local 624. San Raphael, CA, 1964 (Box-folder 4/38)
  - Local 628. Philadelphia, PA, 1966 (Box-folder 4/39)
  - Local 629., 1965 (Box-folder 4/40)
  - Local 631. Las Vegas, NV, 1964 (Box-folder 4/41)
  - Local 636. Pittsburgh, PA, 1963 (Box-folder 4/42)
  - Local 640., 1965 (Box-folder 4/43)
  - Local 655. Redwood City, CA, 1962 (Box-folder 4/44)
  - Local 665. San Francisco, CA, 1961-69 (Box-folder 4/45)
  - Local 684. Eureka, CA, 1965-70 (Box-folder 4/46)
  - Local 692., 1961 (Box-folder 4/47)
  - Local 713. Chicago, IL, 1964 (Box-folder 4/48)
  - Local 741. Seattle, WA, 1962-67 (Box-folder 4/49-50)
  - Local 760. Yakima, WA, 1962 (Box-folder 4/51)
  - Local 768. Hayward, CA, 1968 (Box-folder 4/52)
  - Local 777. Chicago, IL, 1965 (Box-folder 4/53)
  - Local 795., 1961 (Box-folder 4/54)
  - Local 809., 1962-63 (Box-folder 4/55)
  - Local 848. Los Angeles, CA, 1963-66 (Box-folder 4/56)
  - Local 853. Alameda County, CA, 1962-63 (Box-folder 4/57)
  - Local 856. San Francisco, CA, 1956-69 (Box-folder 4/58)
- Charter Applications, undated (Box-folder 4/59)